(Sheldon:)Whereas, you know,
you say Ditko,
(Sheldon:)and that sounds like
a company that makes Dits.
(Leonard:)That's not helping.
(Sheldon:)Well, I'd give more examples,
(Sheldon:)but, well, everyone in
your position's so forgettable.
(Howard:)Stuart, we're here.
(Raj:)It's nice of you to let him keep
staying at your mom's house.
(Howard:)Yeah, well, I tried putting him
out on the curb,
(Howard:)but nobody took him.
(Amy:)Hey.
(Stuart:)Just so you know,
the power's out.
(Bernadette:)What happened?
(Stuart:)I called,
they said a transformer blew.
(Stuart:)It's the whole block.
(Stuart:)Should be fixed by tomorrow.
(Howard:)Wait, when did it go out?
(Stuart:)In the middle of the night.
(Howard:)Oh, my God.
(Bernadette:)Howie, what's wrong?
(Howard:)It's all defrosting.
(Bernadette:)It's okay. It's just food.
(Howard:)It's not just food.
(Howard:)This is the last food
my mother ever made.